Vovoka.space <- contact me now!

NAME VLADIMIR POLANSKY

FRONTEND DEVELOPER BATUMI, GEORGIA

BATUMI, GEORGI

CONTACTS

VOVOKA.SPACE

SKILLS

REACT, GATSBY

TYPESCRIPT, JAVASCRIPT HTML5, (S)CSS, MATERIAL UI

NODE, EXPRESS

MONGODB, GRAPHQL, MYSQL TESTING LIBRARY, JEST GIT, WEBPACK, ESLINT

APP DESIGN BEST PRACTICES, MVC UNDERSTANDING OF UI/UX, AGILE

EXPERIENCE

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

DECEMBER 2021 - PRESENT

REACT, TYPESCRIPT, JAVASCRIPT, NODE.JS, HTML, CSS

I developed over 15 web apps under the multilevel frontend training program of RSS (30-40 hours of practice per week) and several pet

WEDDING/PORTRAIT PHOTOGRAPHER

2011 - 2020

WORDPRESS, HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT, PHP, MYSQL

I created over 10 Wordpress websites. I was doing SEO, UX/UI, product strategy, customer journey, SMM, marketing, sales, Google ads, and communication with foreigners.

EDUCATION

THE ROLLING SCOPES SCHOOL

DECEMBER 2021 - NOVEMBER 2022

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Four Frontend courses: «Preschool», «Stage #1», «Stage #2», «React»

BELARUSIAN STATE AGRARIAN TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY ELECTRICAL ENGINEER

1993 - 1998

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH

INTERMEDIATE (B1)

Keep improving everyday

BELARUSIAN

NATIVE

RUSSIAN

NATIVE

ABOUT

During the year I gained extensive experience and knowledge on how to design an application that will be extensible in the future and convert it into components that can be easily extended and reused. I have experience to deliver results within project's resources and time constraints.

Programming is my passion since I was in school. I love to travel. I've visited 14 countries. I'm happy to meet new people. I like team sports, music and board games.

I think I have good communication skills to articulate thoughts clearly. If I don't know something, I'll go and find out. Then I'll share this knowledge with colleagues.

INTERESTS

PROGRAMMING, CREATING APPS INNOVATIVE TECHNOLOGIES PSYCHOLOGY, HISTORY TRAVEL, MEET NEW PEOPLE BASKETBALL, TABLE TENNIS PLAY GUITAR, BOARD GAMES